I won't let your deaths be meaningless
even if I'm the last one standing
In both hands, Gloria
What sings is Sieg
On my back, Flügel der Freiheit
Clenched determination to my left chest
What slashes across is Linie der Torheit
Soaring across the azure skies
Flügel der Freiheit
"Smile"
"Assault on Stohess, Part 1"
That's it, Annie!
I'd expect no less
from my daughter!
What are you doing, Annie?!
No resting!
"Wall Sina" "Eastern fortified city"
You mean you haven't heard?
The Titan boy and the
big shots in charge of him
"Stohess District"
are apparently being called to the capital.
And they're passing
through this city today.
I see.
Sounds like he'll get dissection
for sure this time around.
Whatever the case, I just hope
he passes through without a hitch
and has the gate
shut firmly behind him.
Did you just
mention sealing the gate?!
You would suggest that we
defile the walls even further?!
Maria! Rose! Sina!
To defile the three goddesses is to
commit an unpardonable transgression!
They love and worship
the walls as gods.
Don't get involved.
Man. They're still around, huh?
Damn...
Our only protectors are the walls!
"Stohess District"
"Military Police Branch"
You're finally up.
You look so totally scary when you're
asleep that I couldn't wake you up.
Sorry, Annie.
You've been slacking a lot lately.
What's this? Are you mad already?
She's antisocial, all right.
Just leave her be.
She came here from Trost.
She's the only one
here who's seen real action.
It'll take time for her to recuperate.
She's just been through hell.
Ah, I get it!
You have a thing for her!
What can you possibly
like about this girl?
Hitch.
There's only one way a ditz like
you could get into the Military Police.
Oh? Whatever do you mean by that?
--Say it to my face.
--Enough, you two!
Oh, take it easy, guys.
I have actual work for you today,
instead of the usual odd jobs.
That's why I called you here.
It's to do with the Scout Regiment
group being summoned to the capital.
They're passing through
this town's main street today.
Military Police HQ will be
serving as their security escorts,
so we need only assist
while they pass through.
Omni-directional mobility within
city limits is temporarily authorized.
You'll follow beside the
convoy and help bolster security.
You'll also head to
the starting point by barge.
That is all.
May I ask something, Sir?
Hmm? What is it?
What are we supposed
to protect the convoy from?
I've never heard of anyone inside
this wall defying the royal government.
There may be petty criminals,
but I can't imagine actual
organizations trying anything
unless they're based
outside the wall...
I'm not even sure
what motive they'd have.
Oh, you're a serious one!
You're in charge now.
The details are all in here.
Huh?
We officers are busy enough as it is.
Prove that you can handle this yourselves.
But no screw-ups. Got it?
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Shall we continue?
Whose turn is it again?
Damn! This is messed up!
Yeah, this organization's
way more rotten than I'd imagined.
Well, that is why I chose it,
but you get stuck doing all the
work when you're a rookie here...
Man, why didn't anyone tell me?
Bastard...
All he can think about is himself!
Huh? What are you talking about, Marlo?
Choosing to join the Military Police
makes you no different from him.
No. I'm nothing like you degenerates.
I came here to fix the Military Police!
Wow, Marlo!
I never took you for that sorta guy!
How are you gonna fix it?
By getting to the top, of course.
Once I'm at the top, I'll fix the rules
and make the dishonest
pay fairly for their injustices.
It's that simple!
I'll simply turn them back
into normal people. That's all.
Back into the people
they're supposed to be.
Oh, man! You're the real deal!
Sorry! I originally took
you for a stick-in-the-mud!
That's quite the noble goal.
Good luck with that.
I wonder.
If a do-gooder like you took charge,
I think that would spell the end for us.
Oh, so you can talk?
I think you're an honest person.
Because you say honest things.
I know there are people like that.
It takes a lot of courage
to go against the flow.
I respect that.
It could just be that
you're all fools, though.
No, maybe they are,
but don't lump me in with them!
Enough of this chit-chat. Let's go!
The escort wagons will pass through
the outer gate in forty-five minutes.
When we get there, find your positions.
--Understood?
--Yeah, yeah...
Hey, now!
What's that?
That's our equipment!
Must be taking it into the interior.
Still, it's strange for the merchant
association to be involved.
Just what are they...?
They're illegally selling
government-issued equipment?!
Hey, now! What about
our assignment?!
Oh, man! He's the genuine article!
Well, for better or worse, we do have time.
This'll make for some nice entertainment.
So, how about a drink?
Yeah? What do you want, rookie?
I-It's against the law to
sell government property.
So?
Government property is paid for
by the citizens' hard-earned tax money.
Therefore--!
Wow, a rookie blackmailing
his superior officers...
You got a bright future in store, you do.
Go get yourself a girl or
somethin' and refresh yourself.
Wha...?!
W-Wait!
It's against the law to sell--
Hey!
You're under arrest for a treasonable
offense against a superior.
D-Don't be stupid...
Such disrespect for the law...
...is perfectly acceptable.
Here, anyway!
I think that's enough, don't you?
So sorry about that!
It seems our idiot has caused you trouble...
We'll teach him a lesson, don't you worry!
Or...
...would you prefer to have an
even bigger problem on your hands?
Just this once.
Yes, Sir!
--Now, let's get that drink.
--Yeah. I'd say we earned it.
Go on.
You're going to make the dishonest
pay for their injustices, right?
I'm not against helping
you out with that...
Damn it!
You're certainly a hard worker, Missy!
Oh, no, you're too kind!
Those people you know...
Those fools you mentioned earlier...
Would they have done it?
They might have.
You mentioned going against the flow...
I guess I'm just another piece
of scum being swept away by it.
I don't know.
But maybe that's just
the way ordinary people are?
Personally...
Even if it means being a
weakling swept up in the flow,
being seen as a person is all I want.
Annie.
Hi.
Looks like you're
a full-fledged MP now.
Armin...
Why are you dressed like that?
I'm a cargo carrier.
I'm hiding ODM equipment
under this rain gear.
See?
What is this about?
Annie.
Could you help us let Eren escape?
Escape to where?
Defying the government's orders...
Where is there to run inside these walls?
We just need to hide him for a while.
We won't be explicitly
rebelling against the government;
it'll basically be an act of defiance
by part of the Scout Regiment.
We're going to buy enough time
to gather some things
that will unquestionably overturn
the council's say in the matter.
Overturn it?
There's really something that handy?
How are you so sure?
I'm sorry. I can't say.
Sorry, but I can't accept.
I won't tell anyone, though.
Good luck.
Annie!
Please!
They're going to kill Eren!
A bunch of people who know nothing
are unwittingly pushing humanity
toward the brink of self-extinction
simply to save their own necks!
I realize it sounds less than convincing.
But, even so, we have no
choice but to bet everything now!
Of course, we'll try
hard not to cause you trouble.
But we absolutely need the
Military Police's help
to sneak him through
Wall Sina's security checkpoint.
This is our only option left.
Tell me.
Do I look like that
good of a person to you?
A good person...
Actually...
I've never been fond
of phrasing it that way.
Because, to me,
it feels like it's only used
to refer to people you
use for your own convenience.
And I don't think there's
anyone who's convenient to everyone.
Which is why, if you do say no to this...
...that'd make you a bad person in my eyes.
Okay.
I'll do it.
We got through surprisingly easily...
Shh!
That's the mighty Military Police for you.
Goes to show what kind of work they do...
Don't look around at everything.
Let's just hope they haven't
realized Jean took my place.
That definitely won't last for long.
He and I look nothing alike.
It'll be fine.
You both have the same
sort of mean, nasty look to you.
I don't have his horseface!
Say...
How were you planning to get over the wall
if I hadn't agreed to help?
We were going to barge through using ODM.
That's crazy.
Couldn't you have just
escaped before reaching Stohess
to avoid all this trouble in the first place?
Why'd it have to be here and now?
I felt this town's complex layout
would make our body double
ploy more likely to succeed.
Plus, acting dutifully and
keeping their defenses down
will buy us far more time to escape
than head-on opposition would.
I see. Good point.
Oh! Over there!
Here?
Yeah. We're going through here.
It's what's left of an underground
city they were planning to make.
It leads to the vicinity of the outer gate.
Really? That's amazing.
Annie?
Oh, man.
Don't tell me you're afraid of dark,
cramped places or something...
Yes. I am.
I doubt a brave, suicidal maniac like you
would understand how a delicate damsel feels.
Any damsel who can flip a grown man
upside down isn't weak at all.
Cut the crap! Let's hurry!
No. I'm not going.
I'm afraid to go down there.
I'm not helping unless we
stay above ground.
Quit being stupid! Just get down here!
Stop screwing around!
Eren! Don't shout!
I'm sure it's fine, Mikasa.
Because, for some reason,
this whole area...
...has been completely
deserted for a while.
Man... That really hurts.
At what point did you
start looking at me that way...
...Armin?
Annie...
Why did you have Marco's ODM gear?
It had all the same scrapes and bumps...
I could tell, because I'd
helped him do maintenance on it.
Yes...
I found it and took it.
Then, those two Titans we captured alive...
Was it you who killed them?
Who knows.
But if that's what you
suspected one month ago,
why didn't you do anything then?
Even now I can hardly believe it...
I just... wanted to believe
I had it all wrong...
That's why I didn't...
Still... Back then...
The fact you didn't kill me back then...
...is why we're in this situation now.
Yeah... I agree with all my heart.
I never imagined you'd
end up cornering me like this.
Why didn't I do anything then...?
Hold on, Annie!
There's still a chance
you're going along with all this
as part of some horrible, idiotic joke!
Just get down here!
There's something you can
prove just by coming down here!
Come down here and prove it!
I can't go down there.
I'm a failed warrior.
I'm being serious here!
This isn't funny!
Talk to us, Annie!
We can still discuss this as--
Enough.
I can't listen to any more of this.
It's pointless.
I'm going to carve you up again...
...Female Titan!
Armin...
It's nice I could be
a "good person" for you.
For now, you've won your bet.
But...
...my bet...
...begins now!
Eren!
Mikasa?!
It's too late...
If, by chance, I'm not me
then who's to say that you're you?
Can you pick up the pieces of your heart
that fell apart like a broken sand castle?
The voice of someone calling out
changed into ringing in my ears
It's as if time has stopped
Now wake up
I made my way out of the deep darkness
I fled like a swift wind
We used to be like living corpses,
but now we head beyond the walls
Let's meet again
in a place not on any map
The Female Titan was actually
Annie Leonhart all along.
However, even when faced with her,
Eren is unable to transform.
Because she's Annie.
"Mercy"
"Assault on Stohess, Part 2"